Good news, everyone!
We've been hired to make
our 100th delivery.
One hundred!
That's almost
10 per year.
This calls for a party, baby.
I'm ordering 100 kegs, 100
hookers and 100 Elvis impersonators
who aren't above a little
hooking, should the occasion arise.
Be very gentle, folks.
This is the soufflй you're
delivering to Mrs. Astor.
Oh, my God, it's Elzar! Hi,
Elzar! Great soufflй, Elzar!
Whatever you do,
don't drop it.
See, Mrs. Astor takes
nitroglycerine for her heart,
and being a class act, she
prefers it in soufflй form.
Bam!
To prevent the soufflй from
exploding, Bender will carry it.
He's gyroscopically stable.
Look! Mrs. Astor's mansion, just
across that rickety rope bridge.
Wow, it's ricketier
than it looks.
You better try
to jump it, Bender.
Okay, let me back up
for a running start.
Here I go!
I shall inform Mrs. Astor
that the circus is in town.
Your soufflй, madam.
I shall take it here,
under my fork.
Where's the exploding?
One does not explode
in Mrs. Astor's face.
I couldn't eat another bite. Hobsie?
Well done, sir.
Have you a name?
Hubert Farnsworth,
at your service.
A Farnsworth, you say?
Well, if I'm not mistaken,
the Farnsworths have been in New
New York for almost 200 years.
Yes, I have.
And I'm his uncle.
How charmingly
unconventional.
I can eat a hot dog
underwater.
Say, would you Farnsworths
care to be my guests tomorrow
at the Astor
Endowment Fundraiser?
All the best families
will be there.
We can take them.
On April 10, 2912,
my late husband and I
set off down Fifth Avenue
aboard the Land Titanic,
the largest street-going vessel ever built.
Just four days into her maiden
voyage, as we approached 32nd Street,
the land liner struck a mailbox and went down.
2,000 souls were lost that
day, including my dear husband.
In loving memory, I established
the Mr. Astor Endowment,
which this year supports the
United Mutant Scholarship Fund.
Mutants? That's the kind of thing you are.
Shh. You know mutants aren't
allowed on the surface.
If anyone asks, say I'm an alien, remember?
Right. You gonna
finish that roll?
Shh.
Now, a short film about those pitiable
creatures so in need of our charity.
Far beneath the everyday rumble
of limousines and poodle feet,
there toil
a downtrodden people
even less well off
than the upper middle class.
The noble sewer mutants.
For, you see, generations
of exposure to toxic sewage
mutated them
into horrific monsters!
Shut up.
These industrious,
uh, people, I guess,
maintain the various pipes
and poop chutes
that keep decent, above-ground
society functioning.
And where do these proud toileteers
learn their menial skills?
At Brown University,
the nation's premiere
institution of lower learning.
So please, give generously,
knowing some poor helpless
mutant will thank you.
Not in person, thank God.
Well, that
was disturbing.
I understand, dear.
They are hideous.
Look, I guess you mean well,
but isn't that university
just a tax-deductible
sewer-cleaning service?
My dear, that school is about
much more than sewer pipes.
Really?
It's also about keeping
those filthy things busy.
There are thousands of them
down there, breeding like rats.
My great uncle
once saw a rat.
If we don't
keep them busy,
they'll start jabbering about equal
rights in their ill-bred manner.
Let's go.
If I say one more thing, I might
say it with my evening boot.
Well! Rarely have I never!
Please, don't blame Leela.
She's just a little ill-bred.
You know how mutants are.
Your companion
is a mutant?
But if anyone asks,
say she's an alien.
Help! Police!
You may have
eluded the authorities,
but don't nothing
get past Mrs. Astor.
What's going to
happen to me?
Permanent deportation, you mutant.
You going downtown,
baby. Way down.
Incoming!
Thanks, Colonel.
Just doing
my job, ma'am.
Mom, Dad, I can't believe I have to spend
the rest of my life in this hellhole.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, sweetie.
Now that you're here, this hellhole
feels more like a nice, regular hole.
What do you say we go get some sewer coffee,
sewer cake and
Safeway ice cream.
Well, the bottom's all stocked with cheap stuff.
Who's in the mood
to party?
Whoo!
Poor Leela. I feel
like I ruined her life.
You did ruin her life.
You might be
right, Hermes.
I am right.
I almost feel like we should
do something to help her.
We should do something!
I don't care what you say, Hermes. Let's go.
Oh, mighty Mayor, we're here about Turanga Leela.
You mean Leela?
Right.
I mean, sure, she's a mutant,
we've known that for years,
but we kept it secret 'cause
she's a fine, upstanding...
Wait. You knowingly
attempted to harbor a mutant?
We did
harbor a mutant!
Uh-oh.
Look, Leela,
there's Old Filthful.
Urgh!
And there's the
West Side Pipeway.
If those guys slack off for
even a second, it could explode.
Hey, guys!
This is my daughter, Leela.
Hey.
How you doing?
Well, they're with
the chuds now.
These conditions
are deplorable.
I swear, I hate every single person on the surface
for making us
live like this.
Leela!
What are you
doing here?
We were sentenced to two weeks in
the sewer for harboring a mutant.
$3 at the drugstore.
I'm so sorry
I ratted you out,
but, you know,
after two weeks down here,
I'll truly understand the
plight of the mutant people.
How dare you.
You want to understand
something? Look at that lake.
One dip
in that toxic muck
and your DNA will be
permanently mutated.
You'll grow a camel hump
or a Zoidberg face.
Urgh!
You want to know what it's like to be a mutant?
Jump in
and go for a swim.
I would, but I ate a bunch of potato salad, so...
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You are all surface.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Fry! Hermes!
Where my humans at?
Ah, who cares? It is on.
Hey, hey, hey.
I trust the orgy pit
has been scraped and buttered?
You know it. And there's mini quiches, too.
It's getting cold and smelly. My
Odor-Eaters are going critical.
Maybe we could plotz
in that giant cockle.
Shmeepers,
it's the Land Titanic,
the biggest and onlyest
land boat ever constructed.
This was
one hell of a bus.
Well, everyone debone a
bunk and get some shut-eye.
Zoidberg,
show some respect.
This is a sacred shrine to the
thousands who lost their lives.
Hey, I found a safe.
It's coming loose.
Hand me some more
of that cruise director.
The original
passenger manifest.
Spreadsheets were
so elegant back then.
Just one other item.
It's jewelry. Jewelry!
It's jewelry, people!
It's a priceless
quantum-force gemerald.
What's that
enscribbled on it?
"My dear Mrs. Astor.
"My love for you is as
unsinkable as this land ship
"and as brilliant
as this stone.
"Dictated but not read,
Mr. Astor".
Aw.
That's so valuable.
Yeah, I'll never have love
like that. Leela hates me now.
Did you guys know
I have a crush on Leela?
What's the matter, Leela? You've
hardly touched your toilet clams.
Maybe I was too harsh
on Fry.
He didn't ruin my life
on purpose.
Things will work out,
honey. Now, here.
Have some more of what looks like lemonade.
We can dip left slide right
all night
It's time to be wild
Freestyle
It's on and poppin'
Ain't no stoppin'
Us from rockin'
From tonight to ten o'clock
Bender, I've been to wang dang
doodles all up and down the galaxy,
but this is the dangest wang
I ever doodled.
Oh, yeah!
Come on, baby,
let's do it!
Shake your booty, baby.
Come on! Yeah!
This beat bangs
Here's my chance
Come on, girl, let's go,
I can't...
Get out! Get out! It's not fun
anymore! I want to be alone!
Alone with me?
I said scram, grapey!
Fry? What are you doing?
You were right.
I don't know what it's like to be a mutant.
But I want to know.
Wait. I never
meant for you to...
Oh, no!
Fry! Fry!
No! No!
Any effect?
Sorry. I tried to scream
but I barfed.
I think I'm knowing what it's like to be a mutant.
So what's with all
the screaming?
Hey, guys.
Fry, this is the stupidest,
sweetest thing you've ever done.
And you know,
maybe now, together,
we can be an inspiration
to other mutants.
I hope so, Leela.
Aw. Come here. Let me give you a kiss.
Hug.
Handshake.
I'll text you.
My fellow mutants, until
recently, I dwelt on the surface,
where a man can gaze up at the sky in wonder
without a wet clump
falling in his mouth.
We can do that, too.
Who's ready to fight
for equality?
The devolution revolution
has begun!
Beautiful mutants,
please welcome Devo!
Hello, Sewer City.
As longtime mutants ourselves, we
support your righteous struggle,
and we'll do anything
we can for you!
Play Whip It!
No.
Play the other one.
It's a beautiful world
we live in
A sweet romantic place
Beautiful people everywhere
The way they show they care
Makes me want to say
It's a beautiful world
Ooh!
For you
Now that we've got
their attention,
it's time to hit them
where they sit
by bending the West Side Pipeway
to return all sewage to the surface.
But who could possibly bend such a huge pipe?
So lonely.
Poor, sad Bender.
Hey, buddy.
What the heck?
Bend it! Bend it! Bend it!
What goes down must back up.
Yucks. I picked the wrong day
to wear my new Crocses.
Prepare to storm the surface
for the Million Mutant March!
Move out, Fry.
We need our most disgusting
mutant leading the charge.
I'll meet you up there. I need
to check out something first.
Okay. Vyolet,
you're up front.
Hey!
Mayor, this sewer debacle
has gone on long enough.
As your largest campaign
contributor, I demand action!
Very well.
$80 worth of action it is.
Voilа.
We simply pump the fruits of our
excretion into Madison Cube Garden.
Well, it seems
everything is under...
Two!
Four!
Six eyes!
The mutant people
will arise!
The segregation of the mutant people ends today.
We demand equal rights,
equal access to the surface,
and the blood of
your first-born children.
That's so we have something
to give up in the negotiations.
I've never been so moved, and
I see no reason to begin now.
Hobsie, flush those creatures back
down the hole they crawled out of.
Madam's sewage-seeking
missile.
Let my people stay!
Neat.
Mrs. Astor,
deep in the sewer,
we discovered the wreck
of the Land Titanic,
on which your husband
land-drowned.
Inside was something
that might interest you.
The gemerald ring my husband was
to give me in lieu of children.
So what? I have a chandelier
in my car made of those.
Not the gem.
This passenger manifest.
It turns out there were mutants on that ship
working below deck
in the sewage galley.
Ma'am?
I was just a young girl.
Drain angels,
they called us.
When the ship
started going down,
my mother grabbed me and
made for the nearest life-car.
But the places were all taken
by surface passengers.
As my mother held me tight,
I suddenly felt the gentle
tap of a cane on my face.
I turned to see the kindly smile of Mr. Astor.
Thanks to your
husband's humanity,
I lived to raise my own daughter,
and she, a daughter in turn.
Mom, why have I
never heard this?
My mother's nuts.
I beg you,
Mrs. Astor,
if you truly want to honor your husband's memory,
treat these people
with dignity, as he did.
Oh, he was
a dear man, Mr. Astor.
Randall, let's grant
these mutants their freedom.
Okay.
Are we not men now?
I'm 40% potato,
but close enough.
Thank you, Fry.
I think maybe I can
stomach that kiss now.
What the...
Good afternoon.
I am Mr. Astor.
I did not perish
that fateful day,
but rather plummeted
into the toxic lake,
where I mutated
and lived in solitude
until this ruddy lad here stepped
into my mouth and lodged there.
Mister?
Is that really you?
Hooray! A happy ending
for the rich people!
Mom, Dad, Grandma,
this is where I work.
Oh!
Was there a fire?
So, Bender,
how was the party?
Only the greatest
party ever!
I don't need to have another
party in my whole life.
I am partied out!
Dang.
Sorry we missed it.
We could have another one, if it
would make you guys feel better.
Really? No,
that's not necessary.
Hit it, Bender!
Bend it, bend it
Just a little bit
And take it easy
Show you're likin' it
And, lover, you know
that we're gonna hit
The heights 'cause I'm sure that we're made to fit
Together, just like
pieces of a
Jigsaw puzzle
What's the hustle?